Park Güell: A public park designed by Antoni Gaudí, famous for its colorful mosaics, organic shapes, and panoramic views of the city.
Park Güell: Un parc públic dissenyat per Antoni Gaudí, famós pels seus mosaics acolorits, formes orgàniques i vistes panoràmiques de la ciutat.
Port Vell: The old port of Barcelona, now a leisure area with an aquarium, restaurants, and shops.
Port Vell: El vell port de Barcelona, ara una zona d'oci amb un aquari, restaurants i botigues.
Sagrada Familia: The iconic basilica designed by Gaudí, a masterpiece of Catalan modernism still under construction.
Sagrada Família: La basílica icònica dissenyada per Gaudí, una obra mestra del modernisme català encara en construcció.
Park Güell: A public park designed by Antoni Gaudí, famous for its colorful mosaics, organic shapes, and panoramic views of the city.
Park Güell: Un parc públic dissenyat per Antoni Gaudí, famós pels seus mosaics acolorits, formes orgàniques i vistes panoràmiques de la ciutat.
Military Government of Barcelona: A historic building that has had various military uses throughout its history.
Govern Militar de Barcelona: Edifici històric que ha tingut diversos usos militars al llarg de la seva història.
Passeig de Lluís Companys: An elegant pedestrian promenade with an Arc de Triomf, gardens, and monuments.
Passeig de Lluís Companys: Un elegant passeig per vianants amb un arc de triomf, jardins i monuments.
Port Vell: The old port of Barcelona, now a leisure area with an aquarium, restaurants, and shops.
Port Vell: El vell port de Barcelona, ara una zona d'oci amb un aquari, restaurants i botigues.
National Palace of Montjuïc: An impressive palace on Montjuïc hill, home to the National Art Museum of Catalonia (MNAC).
Palau Nacional de Montjuïc: Un impressionant palau a la muntanya de Montjuïc, que acull el Museu Nacional d'Art de Catalunya (MNAC).
Park Güell: A public park designed by Antoni Gaudí, famous for its colorful mosaics, organic shapes, and panoramic views of the city.
Park Güell: Un parc públic dissenyat per Antoni Gaudí, famós pels seus mosaics acolorits, formes orgàniques i vistes panoràmiques de la ciutat.
Passeig de Gràcia: An elegant avenue with luxury shops and modernist buildings such as Casa Batlló and La Pedrera.
Passeig de Gràcia: Una avinguda elegant amb botigues de luxe i edificis modernistes com la Casa Batlló i La Pedrera.
Captaincy General of Barcelona: A historic military building located near Las Ramblas.
Capitania General de Barcelona: Edifici militar històric, situat a prop de les Rambles.
Plaça de Catalunya: The heart of Barcelona, a large square with fountains, statues, and shops.
Plaça de Catalunya: El cor de Barcelona, una gran plaça amb fonts, estàtues i botigues.
Seafront Promenade: A long area along Barcelona’s beaches, ideal for walking, sports, or enjoying sea views.
Passeig marítim: Àrea extensa que envolta les platges de Barcelona, ideal per passejar, fer esport o gaudir de les vistes al mar.
Barceloneta Beach: One of Barcelona’s most popular beaches, known for its lively atmosphere and seafood restaurants.
Platja de la Barceloneta: Una de les platges més populars de Barcelona, coneguda pel seu ambient animat i els seus restaurants de peix.
Olympic Port: A marina built for the 1992 Olympic Games, featuring restaurants, bars, and nightclubs.
Port Olímpic: Un port esportiu construït per als Jocs Olímpics de 1992, amb restaurants, bars i discoteques.
Expiatory Temple of the Sacred Heart: A church at the top of Tibidabo, with a statue of Christ and panoramic city views.
Temple Expiatori del Sagrat Cor: Una església al cim del Tibidabo, amb una estàtua de Crist i vistes panoràmiques de la ciutat.
Plaça d'Espanya: A large square featuring the Magic Fountain, the MNAC, and the Venetian Towers.
Plaça d'Espanya: Una gran plaça amb la Font Màgica, el MNAC i les Torres Venezianes.
Magic Fountain of Montjuïc: A spectacular fountain with light and music shows, located on Montjuïc hill.
Font Màgica de Montjuïc: Una font espectacular amb jocs de llums i música, situada a la muntanya de Montjuïc.
Arc de Triomf: Built as the main entrance to the 1888 Barcelona Universal Exposition.
Arc de Triomf: Construït com a entrada principal a l'exposició universal de Barcelona de 1888.
Port Vell: The old port of Barcelona, now a leisure area with an aquarium, restaurants, and shops.
Port Vell: El vell port de Barcelona, ara una zona